<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PUBG Tips</string>

    <!-- Test Ads -->
    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
    <string name="banner_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="interstitial_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>

    <!--Genuine Ads-->
    <!--    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-5225299964519935~1292643053</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="banner_id">ca-app-pub-5225299964519935/5412346300</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="interstitial_id">ca-app-pub-5225299964519935/2115905604</string>-->


    <string name="get_start_text">
        "PUBG’s mobile versions, both for Android and iPhone, "
        "translate large-scale battle royale to the small screen remarkably well—and best of all, "
        "they’re completely free."
    </string>
    <string name="tips_text">
        "Read our guide on how to become a master of Player Unknown\'s Battlegrounds on mobile."
        "Our top tips and tricks for PUBG to help you get …"
        "Check out the full list of PUBG Mobile tips and tricks to learn where to land,"
        "important loot, and other tips for beginners and experts!"
    </string>
    <string name="weapon_tire_list_text">
        "Welcome to our PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds Best Weapons Tier List."
        "You can view the TOP 3 Best Guns in PUBG for each weapon type, like Snipers, Assault Rifles, and even Shotguns."
        "The PUBG Best Weapons Tier List is based on accumulated weapons stats"
    </string>
    <string name="ar_description">
        "Click to show whole Assault Rifles (AR) sorted by Rank."
        "The Rank is according to the damage of the Weapon"
    </string>
    <string name="sg_description">
        "Click to show whole Shotgun sorted by Rank."
        "The Rank is according to the damage of the Weapon"
    </string>
    <string name="smg_description">
        "Click to show whole Sub Machine Guns sorted by Rank."
        "The Rank is according to the damage of the Weapon"
    </string>
    <string name="sniper_description">
        "Click to show whole Snipers sorted by Rank."
        "The Rank is according to the damage of the Weapon"
    </string>
    <string name="pistol_description">
        "Click to show whole Pistol sorted by Rank."
        "The Rank is according to the damage of the Weapon"
    </string>
    <string name="grenade_description">
        "Click to show whole Grenade sorted by Rank."
        "The Rank is according to the damage of the Weapon"
    </string>
    <string name="attach_description">
        "Click to show whole Attachments used for corresponding weapons"
    </string>
    <string name="groza_description">
        Found only in supply drops. One of the strongest damage in Assault Rifles.
    </string>
    <string name="m416_description">
        Effective in all situations with high firepower. Equip all attachments to increase damage &amp; usability.
    </string>
    <string name="akm_description">
        This weapon has high damage but has very high recoil so shoot in bursts to control gun movement.
    </string>
    <string name="scarl_description">
        Equip attachments- to control recoil &amp; stability, making this weapon even more powerful.
    </string>
    <string name="m16a4_description">
        Shooting is unstable so fire in bursts to control weapon\'s recoil.
    </string>
    <string name="s12k_description">
        A very beginner-friendly shotgun that is capable of going full-auto for rapid fire shots.
    </string>
    <string name="s686_description">
        Extremely high damage in short range. Effective in close quarter fights where opponents are not fully-equipped.
    </string>
    <string name="s1897_description">
        Powerful in the early game but damage &amp; firepower is lower than most shotguns in-game.
    </string>
    <string name="awm_description">
        Obtainable only through supply drops. Strong damage that can penetrate a Level 3 helmet!
    </string>
    <string name="m24_description">
        Can only get through supply drops. A more powerful version of Kar98K.
    </string>
    <string name="kar98_description">
        Not as powerful as others but accessible and one of the few sniper rifles lootable from the ground.
    </string>
    <string name="sks_description">
        This marksman rifle has large DPS and rapid fire rate but has high recoil.
    </string>
    <string name="slr_description">
        Another marksman rifle with high amount of recoil but has higher damage &amp; fire rate than the SKS.
    </string>
    <string name="mk14_description">
        This DMR is capable of going full-auto and is only available through supply drops.
    </string>
    <string name="mini14_description">
        Not as powerful as other marksman rifles but is easy to use &amp; has low recoil.
    </string>
    <string name="vss_description">
        Weapon comes with built-in suppressor &amp; scope but damage output is low and bullet drop is very high.
    </string>
    <string name="m249_description">
        100-bullet magazine so you can shoot all you can! Reloading is long so reload when out of combat.
    </string>
    <string name="uzi_description">
        Powerful in short range combat. Equip an extended magazine for sustainability.
    </string>
    <string name="ump9_description">
        Can be used as an alternative to an Assault Rifle. Has low fire power but also very stable due to low recoil.
    </string>
    <string name="vector_description">
        Has low magazine capacity so equip an extended magazine to increase sustainability.
    </string>
    <string name="tommy_description">
        Has fast fire rate and not as powerful in mid-long range combat, utilize in short range fights!
    </string>
    <string name="dp28_description">
        Low recoil with a big magazine capacity. Slow reload speed but attachments are unnecessary to be effective.
    </string>
    <string name="p92_description">
        The P92 has balanced stats from its fire power, magazine size, up to its rate of fire. It\'s recoil is not so bad as well
    </string>
    <string name="p1911_description">
        The P1911 is a powerful pistol, dealing 35 damage with every shot.
        Three successful shots and it will have an unarmored player down.
    </string>
    <string name="r1895_description">
        The R1895 is a vintage revolver that utilizes the same ammo as the AKM, GROZA, Kar98K, among others.
        This allows easy loadout management &amp; you don\'t have to search for two separate types of ammo.
    </string>
    <string name="p18c_description">
        The P18C is currently the only handgun that has full auto shooting mode.
        Players can rain bullets on opponents &amp; eliminate them instantly in close range combat
    </string>
    <string name="r45_description">
        The R45 packs a big punch, dealing 46 damage per shot. However, this is counteracted by it\'s relatively slow firing speed.
    </string>
    <string name="win98">
        The Win94 is a unique Sniper Rifle in the fact that it cannot be equipped with any scope.
        This makes it harder to aim and restricts its effectiveness to short- to mid-range.
    </string>
    <string name="stun_grenade">
        Will cause strong disorientation to everyone within the blast radius (~5m)
        in the form of a loud ringing and a strong reduction in framerate.
        It should be noted that the Stun Grenade ignores cover (rocks, walls) and can affect the user,
        making it unsafe to use for clearing buildings.
    </string>
    <string name="frag_grenade">
        Explosive charge to fragment the outer shell of the grenade in a shaped or radial pattern.
    </string>
    <string name="moloto_cocktail">
        This best use for Molotov is an AOE Denial, for example, using the fire from the Molotov on a
        stair case making it difficult for the enemy to cross the choke point from the burning AOE Damage.
    </string>
    <string name="smoke_grenade">
        Temporarily removes battlefield Vision allowing for sneaky reposition or just a good ole plain escape.
    </string>
    <string name="ar_fh">
        Hides the flash effect when the weapon is fired, and by thus making it far harder to see your precise location.
        The hider also provide some recoil reductions.\n
-10.00% Recoil Pattern\n
-10.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-10.00% Vertical Recoil
    </string>
    <string name="ar_comp">
        Counter the recoil of a firearm and prevent the muzzle from climbing due to kickback from the rapid firing.\n
-25.00% Recoil Pattern\n
-10.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-15.00% Vertical Recoil\n
-10.00% Spread Base
    </string>
    <string name="af">
        Reduces horizontal recoil and increases how fast you ADS (Aim Down Sights).\n
-20.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-20.00% Recoil Pattern\n
+10.00% Faster ADS
    </string>
    <string name="vf">
        Reduces horizontal recoil and the spray pattern.\n
-20.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-15.00% Recoil Pattern
    </string>
    <string name="stock">
        Improved accuracy and stability.\n
-10.00% Animation Kick\n
-10.00% Sway\n
-20.00% Recoil Pattern\n
+15.00% Recoil Recovery
    </string>
    <string name="chock">
        The choke makes the shotgun spread less, making longer shots easier.\n
-18.20% Shot Spread\n
+15.40% Shot Speed
    </string>
    <string name="smg_comp">
        Counter the recoil of a firearm and prevent the muzzle from climbing due to kickback from the rapid firing.\n
-25.00% Recoil Pattern\n
-20.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-25.00% Vertical Recoil
    </string>
    <string name="sn_comp">
        Counter the recoil of a firearm and prevent the muzzle from climbing due to kickback from the rapid firing.\n
-25.00% Recoil Pattern\n
-20.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-20.00% Vertical Recoil
    </string>
    <string name="sn_fh">
        Hides the flash effect when the weapon is fired, and by thus making it far harder to see your precise location.
        The hider also provide some recoil reductions.\n
-10.00% Recoil Pattern\n
-10.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-10.00% Vertical Recoil
    </string>
    <string name="smg_fh">
        Hides the flash effect when the weapon is fired, and by thus making it
        far harder to see your precise location. The hider also provide some recoil reductions.\n
-10.00% Recoil Pattern\n
-10.00% Horizontal Recoil\n
-10.00% Vertical Recoil
    </string>
    <string name="stock_uzi">
        Improved accuracy and stability.\n
-20.00% Vertical Recoil\n
-20.00% Recoil Pattern\n
+15.00% Recoil Recovery
    </string>
    <string name="check_pad">
        Improved accuracy and stability.\n
-20.00% Animation Kick\n
-15.00% Sway\n
-20.00% Vertical Recoil
    </string>
    <string name="bl_k">
        Improved accuracy and stability.\n
-30.00% Reload Duration\n
-50.00% Spread Base
    </string>
</resources>
